question_data = [
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "111,111,111 x 111,111,111 = 12,345,678,987,654,321", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "If you could fold a piece of paper in half 50 times, its&#039; thickness will be 3\/4th the distance from the Earth to the Sun.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "E = MC3",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Zero factorial is equal to zero. ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Topology, the complement of an open set is a closed set.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "L&#039;H&ocirc;pital was the mathematician who created the homonymous rule that uses derivatives to evaluate limits with indeterminations.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number &quot;i&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
